// questionsData.js
const questionsData = {
  matemÃ¡ticas: {
    name: "MatemÃ¡ticas",
    emoji: "ğŸ”¢",
    pairs: [
      { question: "2 + 2", answer: "4"},
      { question: "5 - 4", answer: "1"},
      { question: "3 Ã— 2", answer: "6"},
      { question: "8 Ã· 4", answer: "2"},
      { question: "7 + 1", answer: "8"},
      { question: "10 - 5", answer: "5"},
      { question: "4 Ã— 3", answer: "12"},
      { question: "9 Ã· 3", answer: "3"},
      { question: "6 + 4", answer: "10"},
      { question: "15 - 7", answer: "8"},
      { question: "5 Ã— 5", answer: "25"},
      { question: "0 Ã— 1", answer: "0"}
    ]
  },
  inglÃ©s: {
    name: "InglÃ©s", 
    emoji: "ğŸŒ",
    pairs: [
      { question: "Dog", answer: "Perro", answerEmoji: "ğŸ¶" },
      { question: "Cat", answer: "Gato", answerEmoji: "ğŸ±" },
      { question: "House", answer: "Casa", answerEmoji: "ğŸ¡" },
      { question: "Car", answer: "Carro", answerEmoji: "ğŸš—" },
      { question: "Red", answer: "Rojo", answerEmoji: "ğŸ”´" },
      { question: "Blue", answer: "Azul", answerEmoji: "ğŸ”µ" },
      { question: "Book", answer: "Libro", answerEmoji: "ğŸ“–" },
      { question: "Pencil", answer: "LÃ¡piz", answerEmoji: "âœï¸" },
      { question: "School", answer: "Escuela", answerEmoji: "ğŸ«" },
      { question: "Sun", answer: "Sol", answerEmoji: "ğŸŒ" },
      { question: "Water", answer: "Agua", answerEmoji: "ğŸ’§" },
      { question: "Tree", answer: "Ãrbol", answerEmoji: "ğŸŒ³" }
      // { question: "Tree", answer: "Ãrbol", questionEmoji: "ğŸŒ³", answerEmoji: "ğŸŒ²" } Formato anterior
    ]
  }
};

export default questionsData;